atlanta.net 2018-08-31

# Atlanta.net Privacy Policy

## Atlanta Convention and Visitors Bureau Privacy Policy

**This Privacy Policy was last updated on May 24, 2018.**

This Privacy Policy is provided by Atlanta Convention & Visitors Bureau ("ACVB") and applies to information collected from you by ACVB in the operation of its services, such as through the websites and mobile applications operated by ACVB ("ACVB Services"), which include, without limitation, atlanta.net, atlantameetings.com, IAMATL.net, ATLFiles.com, Discover Atlanta: Official Guide and Discover Atlanta 360ATL Tour mobile apps, promotional websites and any associated content, features and functionality including email and RSS feeds made available on ACVB Services. ACVB respects your privacy and confidentiality and maintains this Privacy Policy to help you understand its commitment to safeguard the privacy of the information you provide to ACVB. This Privacy Policy outlines how ACVB collects and uses the information you provide to ACVB. It also explains the choices available to you regarding ACVB’s use of the information you provide to ACVB and how you can access and update this information.

**Collection of Your Personal Information by ACVB; Use of Cookies and Tracking Tools**

ACVB's mission is to provide you with personalized services and offerings designed to enhance your Atlanta experience. To do so effectively, ACVB may collect personal information (such as name, address, phone number, e-mail address, and other information) from you and we may do so in the following ways:

(a) directly from your verbal or written submission. If you do not want your personally identifiable information to be collected, please do not submit it.

(b) automatically through ACVB Services, which employ "cookie" and pixel technology, Local Storage, and other tracking tools; provided, however, that ACVB will not employ cookies or pixels to track the use of ACVB Services by users based in the European Union without such users’ consent. Cookies and pixels are small pieces of data stored in files on your computer allowing ACVB Services to track your use of ACVB Services as you visit and revisit such websites and applications. The use of cookies by ACVB Services complies with generally accepted programming standards and practices. Please note that you can choose to block the use of cookies and pixels through settings in your web browser but be advised that certain features of ACVB Services may not work properly without the use of cookies or pixels. ACVB Services are not set up to honor web browser do-not-track settings. “Local Storage” is similar to cookies and provides a way for a website to collect and store information "locally" (i.e., on the user's device rather than on the website’s server) and retrieve it later. Although Local Storage data is not typically sent to a website's servers, in some instances, we may transmit Local Storage data to our servers for the purpose of improving your experience on ACVB Services.

**Use of Your Information by ACVB**

It is the policy of ACVB not to sell, share, transfer, or rent to third parties any information you provide to ACVB, including information you provide through the use of ACVB Services, without your consent except as required by operation of the law or in compliance with legal authorities; provided, however ACVB may share your personal information with certain third parties ("Target Third Parties") without your consent in order to further the purpose for which you voluntarily provide ACVB with the information. Additionally, ACVB engages third party information management service providers, including, but not limited to, customer relationship management providers, to help maintain efficient operations. Because such information management service providers may access our systems, such information management service providers may have access to your information. ACVB does not transfer or relinquish ownership of information maintained about you within ACVB systems and databases to such information management service providers but requires these information management service providers to sign confidentiality agreements to keep all confidential information and other proprietary information found in ACVB systems confidential.

ACVB routinely collects, compiles, and reports statistics and information reflecting the use of ACVB Services and information services in order to enhance membership services, advertising services, improve marketing and promotional efforts, analyze usage of ACVB Services, improve ACVB Services' content and layout, generate aggregate reports on trends, interests and behavior and enhance service offerings.

ACVB may now or in the future work with third parties, including third party advertising networks and website analysis firms, who use cookies, pixels and other tracking technologies to collect non-personally identifiable information when you visit ACVB Services. This non-personally identifiable information, collected through cookies, pixels, Local Storage and other techniques, is often used by these advertising networks to serve you with advertisements tailored to meet your preferences and needs.

From time-to-time, ACVB may operate contests or promotions through ACVB Services or otherwise by itself or with one or more participating or co-sponsoring organizations and the Section below captioned “Contests and Promotions” further addresses certain information collection practices by ACVB and participating and co-sponsoring organizations as part of such contests or promotions.

ACVB reserves the right to take any action ACVB deems prudent or necessary to safeguard ACVB Services and your information in ACVB systems and databases from malicious or unwarranted attack by viruses, hackers, or other miscreants. 

**Links to Third Party Websites**

In an attempt to provide increased value to users of ACVB Services, ACVB Services may link to, or contain links for, third party websites that we do not control or maintain. These may include websites linked to products referenced on ACVB Services or in advertisements on ACVB Services. We are not responsible for the terms and conditions or privacy practices employed by any such third party website accessible from ACVB Services. Access to such third party websites is at your own risk, and we encourage you to read the privacy statements of all third party websites before submitting any personally identifiable information while using such other websites. 

**Changing and Deleting Your Personal Information**

You may request ACVB change or delete your personal information in ACVB systems and databases by submitting a detailed description of the desired action to the following e-mail address: privacy@atlanta.net.

Please note that after ACVB processes a change or deletes your personal information from active ACVB systems and databases, it is possible that non-active residual copies of your information may still exist in ACVB systems and on archive or backup media.

**Your Consent**

Other than for European Union citizens, your use of any of ACVB Services constitutes your consent to the collection and uses described in this Privacy Policy of your information by ACVB (and Target Third Parties, in which case, once such Target Third Party is in possession of your information, we cannot control such Target Third Party's use of your information). If you do not agree with the terms and conditions stated in this Privacy Policy, please do not access or use ACVB Services. 

**Electronic Newsletters**

We offer free, electronic newsletters, updates and e-mail reminders as a service to our registrants, based upon your voluntary subscription. You will only receive an electronic newsletter if you have requested it (opted-in). We may share mailing lists between our clients and members for legitimate business purposes. Additionally, to minimize duplicative e-mails and other electronic messages we do correlate user e-mail addresses with Facebook users through a service provided by Facebook, although it is our understanding that Facebook does not retain any of this data. 

**Mobile Applications (for Smartphones and Tablets)**

We offer free notifications and reminders as a service to users that have installed one of our applications, based upon your voluntary subscription. You will only receive a notification if you have requested it (opted in). At any time, notifications can be turned off by accessing the Settings within the application or through the Settings of the mobile device operating system. We may share application user information with our clients for legitimate business purposes. Additionally, to minimize duplicative electronic messages we do correlate application users with their respective Facebook user profile, through a service provided by Facebook, when consent has been given by the user at the time of login, although it is our understanding that Facebook does not retain any of this data. 

**Children’s Privacy and ACVB Website Age Limitations**

ACVB Services are intended for use by persons aged 18 or older. ACVB does not knowingly allow use of ACVB Services by any person that ACVB believes to be younger than 18. ACVB also does not collect any personally identifiable information from any persons under the age of 18 and if we discover that we have been provided any such information, we will delete this information from our records. 

**Contests and Promotions**

From time-to-time, ACVB may operate contests or promotions through ACVB Services or otherwise by itself or with one or more participating or co-sponsoring organizations. In addition to the official rules that apply to such contest or promotion, ACVB may request information from users of ACVB Services who choose to participate in such contests or promotions. Information requested may include contact information (such as name and address), and demographic information (such as zip code and age). If you choose to participate in one of these contests or promotions, the other participating organizations, co-sponsors and their affiliates may also receive and use the information collected or may collect the information directly, and the use of such information shall be governed by the respective privacy policies of such participating organizations, co-sponsors and their affiliates. Other than for European Union citizens, your participation in a contest or promotion through ACVB Services or otherwise shall be deemed to be consent to the receipt and use of such information by ACVB, as well as these other participating organizations, co-sponsors and their affiliates. 

**Your Questions and Concerns**

If you have questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy or any of ACVB's use of your information, please contact ACVB at the following e-mail address: [privacy@atlanta.net](mailto:privacy@atlanta.net). 

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy, or any part of it, without notice at any time and for any reason. Whenever ACVB changes this Privacy Policy, we will post the updated Privacy Policy on ACVB Services, and we will note at the top of this Privacy Policy the date of the last update, which should alert you to changes in this Privacy Policy since your prior visit to ACVB Services. 

**Governing Law**

This Privacy Policy shall be governed in all respects by the laws of Georgia, without regard to choice of law provisions. 

**ADDITIONAL NOTICES TO CALIFORNIA RESIDENTS**

_Do-Not Track Disclosure_  
At this time, ACVB Services are not set up to honor web browser do-not-track settings. 

_Information on Marketing Disclosures_  
California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits our users who are California residents to request and obtain from us once a year, free of charge, information about the personal information (if any) we disclosed to third parties for direct marketing purposes in the preceding calendar year. If applicable, this information would include a list of the categories of personal information that was shared and the names and addresses of all third parties with which we shared information in the immediately preceding calendar year. If you are a California resident and would like to make such a request, please submit your request in writing to us at: Atlanta Convention & Visitors Bureau, Attn: Privacy Policy Compliance, 233 Peachtree Street, N.E., Suite 1400, Atlanta, GA 30303. 

_Content Removal Requests for Users Under 18 Years Old_  
If you are a user under 18 years of age and reside in California, you may request and obtain removal of, content or information that you have posted on ACVB Services. You may send us any such requests by one of the following methods: (i) by email (writing “Privacy Policy – Removal Request” in the subject line) at [privacy@atlanta.net](mailto:privacy@atlanta.net); or (ii) by writing to us at Atlanta Convention & Visitors Bureau, Attn: Privacy Policy Compliance, 233 Peachtree Street, N.E., Suite 1400, Atlanta, GA 30303. We will review the request and respond promptly. You should be aware that a request to remove content or information posted by you on the Website does not ensure or require complete or comprehensive removal of such content or information from our databases. 

**ADDITIONAL NOTICES TO EUROPEAN UNION CITIZENS**

_Legal Bases for Processing Personal Information of European Union Citizens_  
When processing your personal information, ACVB may rely on one or more of the following legal bases (or other available legal grounds), depending on the circumstances: 

(a) Legitimate Interests – ACVB may process your personal information where ACVB has a legitimate interest in such processing for managing, operating or promoting our business, and that legitimate interest is not overridden by your interests, fundamental rights or freedoms.

(b) Consent – ACVB may process your personal information where ACVB has obtained your consent to the processing. 

(c) Contractual Necessity – ACVB may process your personal information where such processing is necessary in connection with any contract that ACVB has with you.

(d) Legal Requirements – ACVB may process your personal information where such processing is required by applicable law. 

_Disclosures to Third Parties_  
Your personal information will not be disclosed to third parties except for where it is necessary for fulfillment of ACVB’s obligations to you or where ACVB is obliged or permitted to do so by law (including, without limitation, through the terms of any agreement ACVB may have with you), or where ACVB makes disclosures that are otherwise consistent with the uses described in this Privacy Policy.

ACVB may also disclose any information (including personal information) relating to you to law enforcement authorities or any regulatory or government authority in response to any request including requests in connection with the investigation of any suspected illegal activities. 

ACVB reserves the right to transfer any personal information ACVB has about you in the event ACVB sells or transfers all or a portion of our business or assets, or merges with another organization. Should such a sale, transfer or merger occur, ACVB will use reasonable efforts seeking to require that the transferee uses personal information you have provided to ACVB in a manner that is consistent with this Privacy Policy.

ACVB will not sell, resell or lease your personal information to any third parties but ACVB may, if required for the purpose(s) for which your personal information was collected and processed, share it with ACVB partners and/or service providers to enable them to provide their services to ACVB or to you, as applicable. The foregoing are in addition to the other uses described elsewhere in this Privacy Policy.

_Security of Personal Information of European Citizens_  
ACVB has policies and technical and organizational measures in place which are intended to safeguard and protect your personal information against unauthorized access, accidental loss, improper use and disclosure. However, you should be aware that information transmitted over the internet is not completely secure because of the nature of the internet and that systems and measures used to secure information are not flawless. For these reasons, although ACVB will use reasonable efforts to protect your personal information, ACVB does not warrant the security of personal information transmitted to ACVB or stored by ACVB, and personal information that is transmitted to ACVB by you electronically is done at your own risk. 

_Retention of Personal Information of European Citizens_  
ACVB’s policy is to retain your personal information only for as long as is necessary to fulfill the purposes for which ACVB collected such personal information, including for the purposes of satisfying any professional, legal, accounting or reporting requirements to which ACVB is subject. To determine the appropriate retention period for personal information, ACVB considers the scope, nature and sensitivity of the personal information, the potential risk of harm from unauthorized use or disclosure of the personal information, the purposes for which ACVB collected and processed your personal information and whether ACVB can achieve those purposes through other means, and any applicable legal and professional requirements. 

_Your Rights as a European Citizen_  
You have a number of rights concerning your personal information that ACVB holds and uses, including the following: 

(a) Right of Access – You have the right to be informed about what personal information ACVB holds about you and to a copy of this personal information.

(b) Right to Rectification – You have the right to have any inaccurate personal information which ACVB holds about you updated or corrected. 

(c) Right to Erasure – In certain circumstances you may request that ACVB delete the personal information that ACVB holds about you.

(d) Right to Complain – You have the right to lodge a complaint regarding the processing of your personal information to an applicable governmental or supervisory authority in your country. 

(e) Right to Withdraw Consent – Where processing of personal information is based on your consent, you have the right to withdraw such consent at any time.

(f) Right to Object – Where ACVB relies on our legitimate interests to process your personal information, you have the right to object to such use and ACVB is required to discontinue such processing unless ACVB can demonstrate an overriding legitimate interest in such processing.

(g) Right to Restriction – You have the right to request that ACVB stop using your personal information in certain circumstances including if you believe that the personal information ACVB holds about you is inaccurate or that ACVB’s use of your personal information is unlawful. If you validly exercise this right, ACVB will store your personal information and will not carry out any other processing until the issue is resolved.

You may exercise any of the above requests in writing to [privacy@atlanta.net](mailto:privacy@atlanta.net). You are also free at any time to request that ACVB stop using your personal information for marketing purposes by writing to [privacy@atlanta.net](mailto:privacy@atlanta.net).
